MARCELO ANSELMO SANTOS

Salvador, Brazil | Phone: +5571986234017

https://portfolio.hellostudio.com.br

☐ https://github.com/PilatusBRX

WEB DEVELOPER | WORDPRESS DEVELOPER | WEB DESIGNER

https://portfolio.hellostudio.com.br

SUMMARY OF QUALIFICATIONS

Web Developer with over 5 years of experience in creating custom, high-performance websites using WordPress. Specialist in developing themes from scratch with ACF, ensuring unique and SEO-optimized solutions.

Experience in integrating with CRMs (Mailchimp, RD Station, Leadlovers) and proficiency in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, ReactJS, TypeScript, and design tools such as Figma.

Always seeking to innovate and deliver projects that exceed client expectations.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Company: Gear SEO

Period: January 2022 to March 2024

Position: Front-end and WordPress Developer

Activities: Responsible for developing websites with custom themes created from scratch, using ACF plugin or created with Elementor, Elementor Pro, and Crocoblock, maintaining existing sites, performing performance and SEO tasks. Experience in various types of websites, such as portfolios, online stores, blogs, corporate websites, and landing pages.

Company: Coopers Digital Production Period: January 2021 to December 2021 Position: **Desenvolvedor Wordpress**

Activities: Responsible for developing websites with custom themes created from scratch, using ACF plugin or created with Elementor, Elementor Pro, and Crocoblock, maintaining existing sites, performing performance tasks. Experience in various types of websites, such as portfolios, online stores, blogs, corporate websites, and landing pages.

Company: PH Digital Soluções

Period: January 2020 to December 2020

Position: Web designer

Activities: Performing regular updates of themes, plugins, and WordPress Core to ensure security, stability, and compatibility. Bug fixing and error correction, performance optimization, and implementation of continuous

improvements.

EDUCATION

Universidade Católica do Salvador

Degree: Portuguese and English Languages

2004 - 2010

ADDITIONAL COURSES

Advanced CSS:

Advanced CSS and Sass: Flexbox, Grid, animations and more.

Duration: 28 hours

Advanced WordPress:

Become a Wordpress Developer - Unlocking Power with code:

Duration: 35 hours

SKILLS

Wordpress Javascript

CSS: Flexbox, CSS Grid, BEM and Sass

Bootstrap and Tailwind

ReactJS and Typescript

SEO techniques for the web

Photoshop

Adobe XD Git and Git Flow

Figma

LANGUAGES

English - Advanced

Spanish - Intermediate